# Omar Ali Mohamed Frontend React.js

✓ omaralimohamedomar1@gmail.com

+20 01286494837

Exemption from military service

https://omaraliomar.netlify.app/

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/omar-ali-9a4076267/

https://github.com/OmarAliBlack4

Bē https://omaraliomar.netlify.app/pages/portfolio

#### **Profile**

Hi, I'm Omar, I'm a passionate software developer. I worked as an Assistant Manager at the Virginia Hotel for 3 years. Afterward, I joined a company called Copy and Print, where I was responsible for fixing Xerox photocopier machines. During this time, I developed a passion for programming and learned front-end. I am very enthusiastic about programming and continuously strive to expand my knowledge and skills in this field.

#### Education

#### Bachelor's degree

Faculty of Business Alexandria university undergraduate 2023 - 2024.

#### **Skills**

HTML CSS

JS BOOTSTRAB

SASS GIT GITHUB

REACT IS Command Line

Computer Skills CS50

# **Projects**

## **Movies Website**

Skills: html - css -js - react - redux - bootstrap - axios - real api .

https://movies-react-project-app.netlify.app/ ☑ : host https://github.com/OmarAliBlack4/movies-app ☑ : code

### **Cart App**

Skills: html - css -js - react - redux tool kit - bootstrap - axios - real api .

https://simple-cart-react.netlify.app/ ☑: host

https://github.com/OmarAliBlack4/cart-app ☐ : code

# **Professional Experience**

2019 – 2021 **Photocopier Engineer** Alex, Egypt Alfa Copy - Copy print

I worked as a Photocopier Engineer at Alfa copy company in 2019.

2017 – 2019 Hotel manager assistant

Matrouh, Egypt Virginia Hotel

I worked as an assistant manager in Matrouh for a period of 3 years.